export const QuizData6 = [
    {
        question: "What is the purpose of responsive design in web development?",
        options:[ "To make websites look good on any device", " To improve search engine optimization (SEO)", " To enhance website security", " A and B only"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What is the goal of user personas in UX design?",
        options:[ "To represent fictional users" , "To identify the target audience" , "To guide design decisions based on user needs " , " Both A and B"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What is the purpose of usability testing in UX design?",
        options: ["To validate design assumptions", "To identify usability issues with real users"," To gather quantitative data on user behavior","B and C"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "What does 'IA' stand for in UX design?",
        options: ["Information Architecture", " Interface Analysis", " Interaction Adaptation", " Interface Accessibility "],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question: "Which method is commonly used to gather user feedback during the design process?",
        options: ["Surveys", " Interviews", "  Observations", " All of the above"],
        answer:4
    },
    {
        question: "What is the purpose of wireframing in UI design?",
        options: ["  To create high-fidelity prototypes", " To define the visual hierarchy of a page","To test usability with real users","To present a finished design to stakeholders"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is NOT a principle of UI design?",
        options: [" Consistency", "Simplicity", "  Complexity", "Clarity"],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question: "What does the term 'user flow' refer to in UX design?",
        options: ["  User Interface", "User Interaction", "User Information", "User Integration"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question: "In UX design, what does the term 'affordance' refer to?",
        options: [" The appearance of an element", "The perceived functionality of an object based on its design"," The speed of a website or application","The arrangement of elements on a page"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question: "Which design tool is commonly used for creating interactive prototypes in UX design?",
        options: [" Adobe Photoshop", "Sketch", "Figma", "Microsoft Word"],
        answer:3
    }

];